[
  {
    "question": "What was the score in the Euro 2012 final?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "2-0",
      "3-0",
      "4-0",
      "5-0"
    ],
    "correct": "4-0",
    "source": "https://ahaslides.com/blog/multiple-choice-football-quiz/"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the Man of the Match award in the 2014 World Cup final?",
    "answers": [
      "Mario Goetze",
      "Sergio Aguero",
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Bastian Schweinsteiger"
    ],
    "correct": "Emperor Meiji"
  },
  {
    "question": "Against which country did Wayne Rooney break the England goalscoring record?",
    "answers": [
      "Switzerland",
      "San Marino",
      "Lithuania",
      "Slovenia"
    ],
    "correct": "Switzerland"
  },
  {
    "question": "After losing a key player in the first game, which team went onto the semi-finals of Euro 2020?",
    "answers": [
      "Denmark",
      "Spain",
      "Wales",
      "England"
    ],
    "correct": "Denmark"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which footballer holds the record for the highest number of assists in the Premier League?",
    "answers": [
      "Cesc Fabregas",
      "Ryan Giggs",
      "Frank Lampard",
      "Paul Scholes"
    ],
    "correct": "Ryan Giggs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which former Belarus international played for Arsenal between 2005 and 2008?",
    "answers": [
      "Alexander Hleb",
      "Maksim Romaschenko",
      "Valyantsin Byalkevich",
      "Yuri Zhenov"
    ],
    "correct": "Alexander Hleb"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jamie Vardy was signed by Leicester from which non-league side?",
    "answers": [
      "Ketting Town",
      "Alfreton Town",
      "Grimsby Town",
      "Fleetwood Town"
    ],
    "correct": "Fleetwood Town"
  },
  {
    "question": "Chelsea beat which team 8-0 to secure the 2009-10 Premier League title on the final day of the season?",
    "answers": [
      "Blackburn",
      "Hull",
      "Wigan",
      "Norwich"
    ],
    "correct": "Wigan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the current top scorer in the UEFA Champions League?",
    "answers": [
      "Alan Shearer",
      "Thierry Henry",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Robert Lewandowski"
    ],
    "correct": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Manchester United beat which team in the 2017 Europa League final?",
    "answers": [
      "Villarreal",
      "Chelsea",
      "Ajax",
      "Borussia Dortmund"
    ],
    "correct": "Ajax"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gareth Bale’s breakthrough moment came in the 2010-11 season, when he scored a second half hat-trick against which team?",
    "answers": [
      "Inter Milan",
      "AC Milan",
      "Juventus",
      "Napoli"
    ],
    "correct": "Inter Milan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team did Porto beat in the 2004 Champions League final?",
    "answers": [
      "Bayern Munich",
      "Deportivo La Coruña",
      "Barcelona",
      "Monaco"
    ],
    "correct": "Monaco"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Serbian team scored beat Marseille on penalties to secure the 1991 European Cup?",
    "answers": [
      "Slavia Prague",
      "Red Star Belgrade",
      "Galatasaray",
      "Spartak Trnava"
    ],
    "correct": "Red Star Belgrade"
  },
  {
    "question": "David Beckham became president of which newly founded club in 2018?",
    "answers": [
      "Bergamo Calcio",
      "Inter Miami",
      "West London Blue",
      "The Potteries"
    ],
    "correct": "Inter Miami"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2011, a 5th tier match in Argentina saw a record number of red cards. How many were given out?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "11",
      "22",
      "36"
    ],
    "correct": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "You can find the oldest footballer in the world playing in which country?",
    "answers": [
      "Malaysia",
      "Ecudaor",
      "Japan",
      "South Africa"
    ],
    "correct": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which overseas British territory became an official Fifa member in 2016?",
    "answers": [
      "Pitcairn Islands",
      "Bermuda",
      "Cayman Islands",
      "Gibraltar"
    ],
    "correct": "Gibraltar"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has won the African Cup of Nations a record 7 times?",
    "answers": [
      "Cameroon",
      "Egypt",
      "Senegal",
      "Ghana"
    ],
    "correct": "Egypt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct option instead of three dots: \"... итоги встречи, президент компании высказал свою удовлетворенность ее результатами.\"",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Проведя",
      "Заведя",
      "Подводя"
    ],
    "correct": "Подводя",
    "source": "https://mgu-russian.com/en/learn/test-online/28/"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct option instead of three dots:\"Мы готовы предоставить дополнительную информацию ...\"",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "в случае необходимости",
      "если надо",
      "если необходимо"
    ],
    "correct": "в случае необходимости"
  }
]